# TETIANA VDOVYCHENKO

Phone:

+380 95 321 7810

**Email:** 

t.vdovychenko.letters@gmail.com

Birth Date: 26.03.1998

#### Summary

GitHub - https://github.com/Js21study

Skills

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript Client Scripting: React, Angular Server Scripting: Node.js, Next.js Front-end: HTML5, CSS3, Sass

Responsive design: Bootstrap, MUI, Tailwind

DB: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL

Other: Redux Toolkit, Zustand, React Query. Some experience with Python(Django),

PHP(Laravel)

#### Experience

#### 11/2022 to 05/2023 - Front-End React Developer (work on project):

- developing components and elements with React + Typescript
- working with Redux Toolkit state manager
- using Figma, Sass, Bootstrap, creating pages for web and mobile version

#### 05/2023 to 08/2023 - Front-End Developer (freelance):

- developing components with Figma
- creating pages with Angular, using Figma

#### 08/2023 to 01/2024 - Front-End React Developer (work on project):

- developing components and elements with React + Typescript
- working with Zustand state manager + React Query
- using Figma, Sass, creating pages for web and mobile version

#### 02/2024 and till today - Full-Stack Developer (freelance):

- developing web-sites with React + Typescript and Node.js + MongoDB
- creating apps with Next.js and Tailwind

#### Education

Degree: Bachelor of Science: Finance and Credit, Borys Grinchenko Kyiv University, 2019

#### Languages

English: Advanced C1 (conversational English)

German (Deutsch): Basic A2

Ukrainian: Native Russian: Fluent

#### Certifications

React JS: ItGid, October 15, 2022

2018 - 2022 @ http://itgid.info

## CERTIFICATE

of completion

Tetiana Vdovychenko

SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETED THE COURSE

React.JS



October 15, 2022



fainer

certificate number : kqnzujx71e1v

### REACT

- 1. Frontend for E-Commerce **online-shop** project with using React, Typescript, Redux-Toolkit, React-Router-Dom, Axios, Debounce, React-Paginate, Sass, Tailwind, Local Storage. (Adaptive Web Design)
  - Project with pagination, filters, sorting, getting items from api, adding items to cart, changing amount of items in cart, deleting from cart and some calculation.
    - Link on GitHub <a href="https://github.com/Js21study/online-shop-typescript">https://github.com/Js21study/online-shop-typescript</a>
    - Link on Versel where you can see this project <a href="https://oline-shop-x4gf.vercel.app/">https://oline-shop-x4gf.vercel.app/</a>
- 2. Frontend for **to-do-list** project in React with using React, Typescript, Redux-Toolkit, React-Router-Dom, React-Hook-Form, React-Bootsrap, Yup. Also this project has different branches with using Tailwind and Storybook. Project with creating, editing, deleting and archiving notes and some calculation (Not Adaptive Web Design, Strong validation)
  - Link on GitHub <a href="https://github.com/Js21study/React-Typescript-Create-Notes-App">https://github.com/Js21study/React-Typescript-Create-Notes-App</a>
  - Link on Versel where you can see this project <a href="https://react-typescript-create-notes-app.vercel.app/">https://react-typescript-create-notes-app.vercel.app/</a>
- 3. Frontend for **form-with-steps** project in React with using React-Router-Dom, Mui, Libphonenumber-js, React-confetti, React-dropzone, React-hook-form, Yup. Multistep form with validations, phone validation with Libfonumber-js, downloading file, memorization of data in context with states (Adaptive Web Design, Strong validation)
  - Link on GitHub <a href="https://github.com/Js21study/ReactHookForm-with-steps">https://github.com/Js21study/ReactHookForm-with-steps</a>
  - Link on Versel where you can see this project <a href="https://react-hook-form-with-steps.vercel.app/">https://react-hook-form-with-steps.vercel.app/</a>
- 4. Frontend for **blog** project in React with using Redux-Toolkit, React-Router-Dom, Mui, Axios, React-Markdown, React-simplemde-editor, React-hook-form, Easymde. Project with authorization, registration, and also with creating users, posts and comments, and deleting, editing posts. (Adaptive Web Design, Basic Validation)
  - Link on GitHub https://github.com/Js21study/frontend-for-blog-react
  - Link on Versel where you can see this project <a href="https://frontend-for-blog-react-5br5-7g96b21ul-js21study.vercel.app/">https://frontend-for-blog-react-5br5-7g96b21ul-js21study.vercel.app/</a>

## **Node**

- 5. Backend for **blog** project with authorization with jwt-token, registration and making posts, with creating users, posts, comments and tags, editing and deleting posts, getting new posts and popular posts, getting one post, getting all posts by tag, counting views and comments. Here were connected 3 Tables: Users, Posts and Comments. Project in Node.js with using Express, Mongoose, Bcrypt, Jwt, Express-validator, Cors, Multer.
  - Link on GitHub <a href="https://github.com/Js21study/backend-for-blog-node-js">https://github.com/Js21study/backend-for-blog-node-js</a>
  - Link on Versel where you can see this project <a href="https://frontend-for-blog-react-5br5-7g96b21ul-js21study.vercel.app/">https://frontend-for-blog-react-5br5-7g96b21ul-js21study.vercel.app/</a>
- 6. Backend for **to-do-list** project with creating, editing, deleting and archiving notes in Node.js and some calculation with using TypeScript, Express, Mongoose, Express-validator.
  - Link on GitHub <a href="https://github.com/Js21study/Backend-For-Create-Notes-App">https://github.com/Js21study/Backend-For-Create-Notes-App</a>

Password for MongoDB - 12345qwerty

More projects on my GitHub <a href="https://github.com/Js21study">https://github.com/Js21study</a>